export const QuizData = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question:
      "Do you consider yourself a Star Wars fan? (does not count towards final score)",
    options: ["Yes", "Yes", "Yes", "Yes"],
    answer: "Yes",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What did Luke Skywalker lose in his fight with Darth Vader?",
    options: [
      "His left hand",
      "His left foot",
      "His right hand",
      "His right foot",
    ],
    answer: "His right hand",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "According to the Emperor, what was Luke Skywalker’s weakness?",
    options: [
      "His faith in the Light Side of the Force",
      "His faith in his friends",
      "His lack of vision",
      "His resistance to the Dark Side of the Force",
    ],
    answer: "His faith in his friends",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "What did Jar Jar Binks end up owing Qui-Gon Jinn after being rescued by the same during the invasion of Naboo?",
    options: [
      "A trip to Otoh Gunga",
      "A Bongo",
      "An honor debt",
      "9,000 credits",
    ],
    answer: "An honor debt",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What is Chewbacca’s weapon of choice?",
    options: ["Blaster Riffle", "Lightsaber", "Metal Club", "Bowcaster"],
    answer: "Bowcaster",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "What’s the name of the spiky-headed Sith Lord holding a cool double-blade lightsaber?",
    options: ["Darth Vader", "Darth Brooks", "Darth Maul", "Darth Paul"],
    answer: "Darth Maul",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "What are the creatures, living on Endor, that helped the Rebel’s to defeat the second Death Star?",
    options: ["Ewoks", "Wookies", "Nerf Herders", "Jawas"],
    answer: "Ewoks",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Who adopted Padmé Amidala’s daughter?",
    options: [
      "Captian Antilles",
      "Bail Organa",
      "Owen and Beru Lars",
      "Giddean Danu",
    ],
    answer: "Bail Organa",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is Admiral Ackbar’s famous phrase?",
    options: [
      "Thats a good wrap",
      "Run!",
      "Its a trap!",
      "Get us out of here!",
    ],
    answer: "Its a trap!",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "What was the job that Finn told Han Solo he had at Starkiller base?",
    options: ["Pilot", "Gaurd", "Chef", "Sanitation"],
    answer: "Sanitation",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "C-3P0 is fluent in how many languages?",
    options: [
      "Over 1,000",
      "Over 90,000",
      "Over 10,000,000",
      "Over 60,000,000",
    ],
    answer: "Over 60,000,000",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "How tall is Chewbacca?",
    options: ["215 cm", "228 cm", "255 cm", "302 cm"],
    answer: "228 cm",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Who was Count Dooku’s padawan before he left the Jedi?",
    options: ["Luke Skywalker", "Anakin Skywalker", "Plo Koon", "Qui-Gon-Jinn"],
    answer: "Qui-Gon-Jinn",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question:
      "In Return of The Jedi, what planet is the second Death Star orbiting?",
    options: ["Endor", "Naboo", "Hoth", "Alderaan"],
    answer: "Endor",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "What did Han and Luke ride on in the snow while in Hoth?",
    options: ["Dewback", "Blurrg", "Tauntaun", "Bantha"],
    answer: "Tauntaun",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "Who is the creator of Star Wars?",
    options: [
      "J.J. Abrahms",
      "George Lucas",
      "Kathleen Kennedy",
      "Dave Filoni",
    ],
    answer: "George Lucas",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question:
      "According to Yoda, there are always how many Sith Lords…no more, no less?",
    options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
    answer: "2",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question:
      "The Lion King‘s Mufasa and which Star Wars character were voiced by the same actor (James Earl Jones)?",
    options: ["Chewbacca", "Boba Fett", "Darth Vader", "Yoda"],
    answer: "Darth Vader",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "Bo-Katan wanted what from Moff Gideon in The Mandalorian?",
    options: ["Credits", "The Darksaber", "Location of Thrawn", "His armor"],
    answer: "The Darksaber",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "What color was Mace Windu’s lightsaber?",
    options: ["Yellow", "Green", "Blue", "Purple"],
    answer: "Purple",
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "According to Luke, confronting what is the destiny of a Jedi?",
    options: ["Fear", "Your enemy", "Darkness", "The Sith"],
    answer: "Fear",
  },
];
